http://www.mohscollege.org/privacy-policy

AboutAbout Mohs SurgeryAbout the ACMSInquiriesNews & NotesPartnersFellowship TrainingMatch ExemptionsGrievance Committee Match PolicyProgram Directors’ RepositoryFellows-in-Training Educational MaterialsFind a SurgeonMembersMembership and DuesAdvocacy and Public PolicyBoard CertificationMohsAIQ RegistryCareer CenterResourcesInformationUpdate Surgeon Finder ProfileMember Research SurveysEducationAbstractsAnnual MeetingPast MeetingsWebinarsPodcastQuestions of the WeekACMS FoundationDonateFoundation PoliciesGrant OpportunitiesMohs Surgeons Leading the FutureHonor Roll of DonorsGivingTuesday
Privacy Policy
The American College of Mohs Surgery (ACMS) has a strong commitment to privacy, recognizing that we are a public association. This statement outlines the policies and procedures concerning information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site, www.mohscollege.org.
Collecting and Using User Information
The ACMS collects information in different ways from those who access our site. We use this information primarily to provide a customized experience as you use our site and, do not share this information with third parties. However, we may disclose personal information collected if we have received your permission beforehand or in very special circumstances, such as when we believe that such disclosure is required by law, or in other special cases described below.
Our site uses order forms for customers to request information, products, and services. We collect users’ contact information (e.g., name and e-mail address) and financial information (e.g., account or credit card numbers). Financial information is used to bill the user for products and services and then is deleted from our records in compliance with the Payment Card Industry Data Security Standard (PCI-DSS). Contact information from the order form is used to send orders, contact the user regarding any problems with the order, and to provide the user with information about our association, including promotional materials. Users may opt out of receiving future communications at any time by updating preferences in their user profile; see the Updating User Profile section below.
Membership Directory
Current ACMS members' contact information is made available through the Membership Directory. This information is only available to other current ACMS members. Members may opt out of being listed in the Membership Directory; see the Updating User Profile section below.
Disclosure of Personal Information
It is ACMS policy not to use or share the personal information about users in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses. However, the ACMS may disclose personal information about users, or information regarding your use of our site, for any reason if, in our sole discretion, we believe that it is reasonable to do so, including: to satisfy laws, such as the Electronic Communications Privacy Act, regulations, or governmental or legal requests for such information; to disclose information that is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be violating our Web site Terms of Use or other user policies; to operate the site properly; or to protect the ACMS and its users.
Updating User Profile
Members who have created an account with the ACMS have the ability to update or change all personal information provided. To do so, access your member profile here (member login required) or e-mail info@mohscollege.org with the new information.
Opt In/Out of Communications
The ACMS provides users the opportunity to opt out of receiving communications from us when we request information about the user. To update these preferences, users can visit https://acms.execinc.com/edibo/Profile or e-mail info@mohscollege.org.
Opt In/Out of Membership Directory
We also allow ACMS members to opt out of displaying personal information in the Membership Directory. To update these preferences, users can visit https://acms.execinc.com/edibo/Profile or e-mail info@mohscollege.org.
Security
Our site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control, but we cannot guarantee that our security measures will prevent third-party "hackers" from illegally obtaining this information.
Cookies
A "cookie" is a small data file that can be placed on your hard drive when you visit certain Web sites. The ACMS may use cookies to collect, store, and sometimes track information for statistical purposes, to improve the products and services we provide, or to save your settings and to provide customizable and personalized services. These cookies do not enable third parties to access any of your personal information. Additionally, be aware that if you visit non-ACMS web sites where you are prompted to log in or that are customizable, you may be required to accept cookies. Third parties and other non-ACMS Web sites may also use their own cookies. We do not control use of these cookies and expressly disclaim responsibility for information collected through them.
Links to Other Sites
This site contains links to other sites. The ACMS is not responsible for the privacy practices or content of other Web sites. We encourage you to read the privacy statements of each Web site that collects your personally identifiable information.
Changes to This Policy
The ACMS reserves the right to revise, amend, or modify this Privacy Policy, our Web site Terms of Use, and our other policies and agreements at any time and in any manner. Notice of any revision, amendment, or modification will be posted in accordance with our Web site Terms of Use.
